How are you doing this
app
that they have more here there is a second above this
book investment take it out then it will be successful then I will be lying
at home that this is what happened that
first of all that
15 rupees light is fine give me
something sir just 15 rupees more I will give you
much of it my book its days
sir count
that Steve Smith what happened please sir I want to tell you
Bollywood sir sir please sir you seem to be
well educated then
why are you reducing it gradually
I am doing this growth for you sir a it makes a difference
for me too a whoever has
read it my wife is very helpful so do
one thing come inside let
me talk about your turmeric
hello hello tell me about yourself and BK
these sirs were educated I was
Prashant but he
wanted to grow us he died when
I was 14 years old my
younger brother was eight years old mom was a housewife
so to run the house I had to do this growth work
I left school that
if I had not left my studies sir a
[Music]
And after that Sir I have kept it and
started reading this vegetable
I have just started learning
that from a dream give me a little more to
learn a little more Okay Rajat never stop dreaming and I am
more interested in electrical things so if
you give me this book to read
then I will be thankful Search of it too But
really giver the bank and I need it back in two days
Two days are enough to finish it
Shore 400g small letters Some dreams are
worth fulfilling After we give you
such a dream that after seeing it you feel like fulfilling it then
go Gift Livelihood Coimbatore and gift
that dream to us at your expense By
giving skill based training like electrical repair or office administration in skills at ICICI Academy it is our responsibility to prepare him for a good job a better life
Sir Manoj how is he
Sir is he that I
need
a good letter he has come Sir you have
commissioned Zindagi's channel Thank you all the best
So let's complete it Whatever you like is about to be
completed
[Music]